

Contact information

Email

juananmgz@gmail.com

Dirección

- Salamanca
- Madrid

Teléfono

(+34) 658 01 61 21

Nacionalidad

Española

Enlaces

- juananmgz.github.io
- linkedin.com/in/juananmgz

Competences

Social skills

Quick learning

Commitment

Agile development

Strategy

Initiative

Leadership

Organization

Performance

Responsibility

Teamwork

Languages

Spanish: Native

Inglés: Intermediate Level

More info

Driving Licenseown **Car**

Juan Antonio Muñoz Gómez

FullStack & DevOps Computer Engineer

Specialized in **Web Development & Agile Methodologies**. My goal is to offer clients the best product applying my knowledge and experience. My preferences are **Interface Design & User Experience (UI & UX)** based on **Human-computer Interactioono**.

Experience

Salamanca, Spain Feb 2021 - Jul 2021 Curricular Internships: Electronics and WebApps development

ESALab Research Group

Development of electronic devices linked to responsive lonic + React apps. Used of technologies such as 3D Design and printing, MIDI, MQTT or websockets.

Ciudad Rodrigo, Spain Jun 2020 - Sep 2020 Database management in business administration San Matías Colsuntancy

Educación

Alcalá de Henares, Spain 2021 - Actualmente

Salamanca, Spain 2017 - 2021

Master in Agile Software Web Development
Univeristy of Alcalá de Henares

Degree in Computer Engineering
University of Salamanca

Certificados y cursos

- Scrum Master: Agile project management with Scrum. Viewnext (2021)
- Business and Marketing Plan. Industrial and Intellectual Property. Operations and Human Resources Plan. Fund. General USAL - Plan TCUE (2021)
- Ionic React: Cross-Platform Mobile Development with Ionic 5. Udemy ESALab (2021)

Otras Formaciones

- . English Native Language Immersion. Edinburgh (2014)
- Musical education [+16 years]. Different associations & instructors (2003-Currently)

Competencias

AGILE DEVELOPMENT

• Scrum + Kanban + Lean + XP: Scrum Master. Jira, Taiga, Mic. Project

WEB DEVELOPMENT

- Basic P. Languages: HTML, CSS, JS, TS, JSON, YAML, PHP, Java
- Frontend: NodeJS, Bootstrap, SASS, JQuery, Angular, VueJS, Parallax, React, EJS
- **DevOps & CI/CD**: Docker, Kubernetes, Istio, APIs RESt, GitHub, GitLab, JUnit, Maven, Gradle, Selenium, SonarQube, Heroku, NPM
- BackEnd: Express, Spring, XML, Python, Perl, JPA
- DDBB & Servers: MySQL, MariaFB, Mongo, FireBase, LDAP, ORM / Apache, NGinx
- MockUp & Prototype: Adobe XD, MockUp, WireFrame, Heuristics, IPO/IPM, C.R.A.P.

SOME OTHER SKILLS

- · Graphic design. 3D Design and printing
- Communication protocols
- · Hardware and Electronics
- O. Systems, Networks and Security

Awards

- Honour Mention Final Project Degree, Fund. General USAL (2021)
- TCUE Market Oriented Prototypes Grant, Fund. General USAL (2021)
- Traditional Music Youngth Talent, Aralafolk (2019)

Articles

Listed in orcid.com: 0000-0001-6794-5445